Finding Aid for School of Public Health (University of Michigan) Records 1909-2015 (bulk 1941-2006).
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean Richard Remington, 1969-1981
  - Annual Files, 1980
    - Departments
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1980; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Epidemiology (V. Hawthorne), 1980 (Box 35)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1980 (Box 35)
      - Health Planning and Administration (R. Grosse), 1980; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1980 (Box 35)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Berki), 1980 (Box 35)
      - Population Planning Center (J. Finkle), 1980 (Box 35)
      - Population Planning Program (G. Simmons), 1980 (Box 35)
  - Annual Files, 1981
    - Administration
      - General, 1981 (Box 35)
      - Annual Reports, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Assistant Dean for Curriculum (F. Larkin), 1980 (Box 35)
      - Center for Continuing Education (A. Brown and C. Stewart), 1981; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1981 (Box 35)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1981 (Box 35)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1981 (Box 35)
      - Student, 1981 (Box 35)
      - Student Affairs, 1981 (Box 35)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1981 (Box 36)
      - Continuing Medical Education, 1981 (Box 36)
      - Executive, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - GRIPH, 1981 (Box 36)
      - Human Studies, 1981 (Box 36)
    - Correspondence
      - 1981, 8 folders (Box 36)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1981 (Box 36)
      - Community Health (D. Striffler), 1981
        - Community Mental Health (Baler), 1981 (Box 36)
        - Dental Public Health (Burt), 1981 (Box 36)
        - Family and Child Health (Falkner), 1981 (Box 36)
        - Health Gerontology (Hickey), 1981 (Box 36)
        - Human Nutrition, 1981 (Box 36)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1981; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Epidemiology (V. Hawthorne), 1981 (Box 36)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1981 (Box 36)
      - Health Planning and Administration (R. Grosse), 1981 (Box 36)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1981; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Berki), 1981 (Box 36)
      - Population Planning Center (J. Finkle), 1981 (Box 36)
      - Population Planning Program (G. Simmons), 1981 (Box 36)
- Dean John P. Kirscht, 1982-1983
  The materials of the Dean John P. Kirscht (1982-1983) series run two linear feet and consist of the 1982 and 1983 annual files. These are further arranged into four subseries: Administration, Committees, Correspondence, and Departments. The subseries dealing with internal affairs of the School (Administration, Committees, and Departments) are fairly complete and detailed. The Correspondence deals with external matters and has been put into chronological order by month during processing. The interim nature of Kirscht's position as Dean may be surmised from the thinness of his correspondence.
  - Annual Files, 1982
    - Administration
      - General, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Annual Reports, 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Center for Continuing Education (A. Brown and C. Stewart), 1982; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Students, 1982; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Committees
      - General, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Continuing Medical Education, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Curriculum, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Executive, 1982; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Human Studies, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Masters of Health Services, 1982 (Box 37)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 37)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Community Health (D. Striffler), 1982
        - Community Mental Health (Baler), 1982 (Box 37)
        - Health Gerontology (Hickey), 1982 (Box 37)
        - Human Nutrition (Grinker), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Epidemiology (V. Hawthorne), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Health Planning and Administration (R. Grosse and K. Warner), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Berki), 1982 (Box 37)
      - Population Planning Center, 1982 (Box 37)
      - Population Planning Program (G. Ness), 1982 (Box 37)
  - Annual Files, 1983
    - Administration
      - General, 1983 (Box 37)
      - Annual Reports, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Center for Continuing Education (C. Stewart), 1983 (Box 37)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1983 (Box 37)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1983 (Box 37)
      - Students, 1983 (Box 37)
      - Vice President for Health Affairs, 1973-1981 (Box 37)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1983 (Box 38)
      - Affirmative Action, 1983 (Box 38)
      - Curriculum, 1983 (Box 38)
      - Data Processing, 1983 (Box 38)
      - Executive, 1983; 3 folders (Box 38)
      - Exit Competency Assessment, 1983 (Box 38)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1983 (Box 38)
      - Human Studies, 1983 (Box 38)
    - Correspondence
      - 1983, 5 folders (Box 38)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1983 (Box 38)
      - Community Health (D. Striffler), 1983
        - Dental Public Health (Burt), 1983 (Box 38)
        - Health Gerontology (Hickey), 1983 (Box 38)
        - Human Nutrition (Grinker), 1983 (Box 38)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1983; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Epidemiology (V. Hawthorne), 1983; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1983 (Box 38)
      - Health Planning and Administration (K. Warner), 1983 (Box 38)
      - Hospital Administration (H. Zuckerman), 1983 (Box 38)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Berki), 1983 (Box 38)
      - Population Planning Center (J. Finkle), 1983 (Box 38)
      - Population Planning Program (G. Ness), 1983 (Box 38)
- Dean June E. Osborn, 1984-1989
  The Dean June E. Osborn series (1984-1989, 9.0 linear feet), contains records from the first six years of Osborn's deanship as the first woman to head the School of Public Health. The 1984 annual files include material generated by Dean John Kirscht who served as interim dean until Osborn's appointment in July 1984. Like the series of the predecessor deans, the records are arranged as annual files, with repeated files within each year. The arrangement of the annual files has generally been retained as they were received. These records are noteworthy as they chronicle the rise of AIDS (Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome) and HIV (Human Immunodeficiency Virus) and Dean Osborn's role as an expert on AIDS issues.
  The first three sub-subseries within each of the annual subseries pertain to internal matters within the School of Public Health: Administration, Committees, and Departments. The Administration sub-subseries contains material of broad interest to the entire school such as accreditation, affirmative action, continuing education, development and students. Some topical entries such as AIDS also appear in these files. The Committees sub-subseries contains minutes and related records from committees within the School of Public Health including the Executive Committee. Material in the Departments sub-subseries includes correspondence with faculty members, memoranda, and reports relating to administrative matters and staffing within the individual departments and programs.
  Unlike the earlier accessions, the geographic point of origin filing system for material generated outside the immediate confines of the School of Public Health has been retained in the annual files. This material has been divided into file headings that reflect the filing system as well as the hierarchy of the school's involvement with public health issues: International, National, State, and University. Due to unevenness in the records themselves, not all file headings appear in a given year.
  Although some intuition is needed to access these records, the folder listing contains sufficient detail to make these divisions meaningful. Within the State heading, for example, files are further broken down by cities. Thus, under Lansing will be found records pertaining to the Michigan Department of Public Health and the Governor's Task Force on AIDS. Files in the University sub-subseries reflect the School of Public Health's interaction with other University of Michigan schools, colleges, and administrative units.
  - Annual Files, 1984
    - Administration
      - General, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Affirmative Action, 1984; 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Annual Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 55)
      - Appointments, 1984 (Box 62)
      - Center for Continuing Education, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Memoranda, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Committees
      - Academic Rank Committee, 1984 (Box 62)
      - Animal Care Committee, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Continuing Medical Education, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Deanship Search Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 62)
      - Executive Committee, 1984; 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1984 (Box 55)
      - GRIPH (General Requirements in Public Health), 1984 (Box 55)
      - Human Studies Committee, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Secretary of the Faculty, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell, M. Brown), 1984 (Box 55)
      - Community Health Programs (D. Striffler), 1984
        - Human Nutrition Program (J. Grinker), 1984 (Box 55)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1984 (Box 55)
      - Epidemiology (V. Hawthorne), 1984; 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education (M. Becker), 1984 (Box 55)
      - Health Planning and Administration (K. Warner), 1984 (Box 55)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Berki), 1984
        - MS Program in Clinical Research Design and Statistical Analysis, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Population Planning, 1984 (Box 55)
    - National
      - Miscellaneous States, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Washington, D.C.
        - Center for Disease Control, 1984 (Box 55)
        - Council on Education for Public Health, 1984 (Box 55)
        - Public Health Service, 1984 (Box 55)
    - State
      - Ann Arbor, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Battle Creek, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Lansing, 1984 (Box 55)
    - University
      - Board of Regents, 1984 (Box 55)
      - College of Pharmacy, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Institute of Gerontology, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Medical Center Retreat, October 9, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Office of the President, 1984 (Box 55)
      - School of Nursing (R. Dumas), 1984 (Box 55)
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1984 (Box 55)
      - Vice President for Graduate Studies and Research, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Annual Files, 1985
    - Administration
      - General, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Accreditation
        - Self-Study, 1985 (Box 56)
        - Site Visit, April 1-3, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Annual Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 56)
      - Center for Continuing Education, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Convocation, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Development, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Faculty Development and Teaching Grants, 1985 (Box 56)
      - International Forum Linking Quality, Effect and Efficiency, October 17-18, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Memoranda, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Regent's Fellowships, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Students, 1985 (Box 56)
      - University Seminar, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Women of the University Faculty (Banquet Speech), May 14, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Committees
      - Academic Rank Committee, 1985 (Box 62)
      - Animal Care Committee, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Continuing Medical Education Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Endowment Committee
        - General, 1985 (Box 56)
        - Executive Committee Actions, 1985 (Box 62)
        - Minutes and Summaries, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1985 (Box 56)
      - GRIPH (General Requirements in Public Health), 1985 (Box 56)
      - Human Studies Committee, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Student Affairs Committee, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (M. Brown), 1985 (Box 56)
      - Community Health Programs (B. Burt), 1985
        - Dental Public Health (Accreditation), 1985 (Box 56)
        - Health Gerontology (T. Hickey), 1985 (Box 56)
        - Human Nutrition (J. Grinker), 1985 (Box 56)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1985
        - Michael Brabec, 1985 (Box 62)
        - Occupational Medicine Site Visit, 1985 (Box 56)
        - Toxicology Site Visit, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Epidemiology (V. Hawthorne), 1985; 2 folders (Box 56)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education (B. Israel), 1985
        - AIDS Seminar, December 7, 1985 (Box 56)
      - Health Planning and Administration (K. Warner), 1985 (Box 56)
      - Hospital Administration (H. Zuckerman), 1985 (Box 56)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Berki), 1985 (Box 56)
      - Population Planning, 1985 (Box 56)
    - National
      - Miscellaneous States, 1985 (Box 57)
      - California (Jonas Salk), 1985 (Box 57)
      - Washington, D.C
        - American Public Health Association, 1985 (Box 57)
    - State
      - Ann Arbor
        - General, 1985 (Box 57)
        - National Sanitation Foundation, 1985 (Box 57)
        - VA Health Services Research and Development Program, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Battle Creek
        - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1985 (Box 57)
        - W.K. Kellogg Foundation Site Visit, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Detroit
        - General, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Greater Detroit Area Health Council, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Meeting with Community Leaders, April 1985 (Box 57)
        - Wayne County Health Department, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Lansing
        - General, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Michigan Department of Public Health, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Michigan Health Officers Association, 1985 (Box 57)
        - PBB Press Conference, May 9, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Public Health Advisory Council, 1985 (Box 57)
    - University
      - Campus Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Department of Internal Medicine, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Department of Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Mental Health Research Institute Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Office of the President
        - Lawrence Mathews, 1985 (Box 62)
      - School of Nursing (R. Dumas), 1985 (Box 57)
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs
        - Billy Frye, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Robert Holbrook, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Budget Conference, February 21, 1985 (Box 57)
        - Future Needs Meeting, December 18, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Vice President for Research, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Vice Provost for Medical Affairs, 1985 (Box 57)
  - Annual Files, 1986
    - Administration
      - General, 1986 (Box 58)
      - AIDS Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 58)
      - Annual Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 58)
      - Appointments and Reviews, 1986 (Box 62)
        [Restricted until December 31, 2016 ]
      - Armenian, Haroutune (Visit), 1986 (Box 58)
      - MD/MPH Program, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Memoranda, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Students, 1986 (Box 62)
        [Restricted until December 31, 2061 ]
    - Committees
      - Academic Rank Committee, 1986; 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1986 (Box 58)
        - Minutes, 1986 (Box 58)
      - GRIPH (General Requirements in Public Health), 1986 (Box 58)
      - Human Studies Committee, 1986 (Box 58)
      - OJ/OC Ad Hoc Committee, 1986 (Box 58)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (M. Brown), 1986 (Box 58)
      - Community Health Programs (B. Burt), 1986 (Box 58)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (R. Gray), 1986 (Box 58)
      - Epidemiology (V. Hawthorne), 1986
        - Chairmanship Search Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 62)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Health Planning and Administration, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Health Policy and Administration, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Health Services Management and Policy, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Hospital Administration, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Medical Care Organization (S. Berki), 1986 (Box 58)
      - Population Planning and Industrial Health (J. Finkle), 1986 (Box 58)
    - National
      - Miscellaneous States, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Georgia
        - Center for Disease Control, 1986 (Box 58)
      - New York, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Texas
        - University of Texas School of Public Health Review, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Washington, D.C., 1986 (Box 58)
    - State
      - Battle Creek
        - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Lansing
        - General, 1986 (Box 58)
        - Public Health Advisory Council, 1986; 5 folders (Box 58)
        - Task Force on Alzheimer's Disease, 1986 (Box 58)
        - Task Force on Infant Mortality, 1986 (Box 58)
    - University
      - Conference on the Health Care System of the, 1990s; 1986 (Box 58)
      - Conference on the Teaching of Ethics and Values in the University, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1986 (Box 58)
        - Department of Internal Medicine, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Planning-Budget Conference, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Substance Abuse Center, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs
        - James Duderstadt, 1986 (Box 58)
        - Robert Holbrook, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Vice President for Research, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Vice Provost for Information Technology (D. Van Houweling), 1986 (Box 58)
  - Annual Files, 1987
    - Administration
      - General, 1987 (Box 59)
      - AIDS
        - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 59)
        - AIDS Lecture (PEW Course), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Annual Reports, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Appointments and Reviews, 1987 (Box 63)
        [Restricted until December 31, 2017 ]
      - Christenson, Brith (Visit), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Correspondence (General), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Development (M. Stuck), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Celebration, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Memoranda, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Student Affairs, Office of, 1987; 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Students, 1987 (Box 59)
    - Committees
      - Academic Rank Committee, 1987 (Box 63)
      - Animal Care Committee, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Committee on Data Processing, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1987 (Box 59)
        - Minutes, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Human Studies Committee, 1987 (Box 59)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Community Health Programs (B. Burt), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Epidemiology (D. Schottenfeld), 1987
        - Victor M. Hawthorne New Investigator Research Award Grant, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Health Services Management and Policy, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Population Planning and Industrial Health (J. Finkle), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Public Health Policy and Administration (K. Warner), 1987 (Box 59)
    - International
      - General, 1987 (Box 59)
      - World Health Organization Australian Inter-regional Ministerial AIDS Meeting, 1987 (Box 59)
    - National
      - Georgia
        - Center for Disease Control, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Washington, D.C
        - General, 1987 (Box 59)
        - Council of Education for Public Health, 1987 (Box 59)
    - State
      - Ann Arbor, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Detroit
        - General, 1987 (Box 59)
        - Greater Detroit Area Health Council (AIDS Talk), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Lansing
        - General, 1987 (Box 59)
        - Michigan Department of Public Health, 1987 (Box 59)
        - Public Health Advisory Council, 1987 (Box 59)
        - Task Force on AIDS, 1987 (Box 59)
        - Task Force on Alzheimer's Disease, 1987 (Box 59)
    - University
      - Center for Human Growth and Development, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Howard Hughes Medical Institute Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Institute of Gerontology, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1987 (Box 59)
        - Department of Internal Medicine, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Office of the President, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Presidential Initiatives Fund, 1987; 2 folders (Box 59)
      - School of Natural Resources, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Transplant Policy Center, 1987 (Box 59)
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs (J. Duderstadt), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Vice President for Research (L. Wilson), 1987 (Box 59)
      - Vice Provost for Medical Affairs (G. Zuidema), 1987 (Box 59)
  - Annual Files, 1988
    - Administration
      - General, 1988 (Box 60)
      - AIDS Correspondence
        - A-L, 1987-1988 (Box 60)
        - M-Z, 1987-1988 (Box 60)
        - Foreign, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Appointments and Promotions, 1988; 2 folders (Box 63)
        [Restricted until December 31, 2018 ]
      - Development Office, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Faculty Recruitment Needs, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Genetics and Biology of AIDS, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Public Health Students' Association, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Students (Admission), 1988 (Box 63)
        [Restricted until December 31, 2063 ]
      - Myron Wegman 80th Birthday Celebration, September 9, 1988 (Box 60)
    - Committees
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1988 (Box 60)
        - Minutes, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1988 (Box 60)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Community Health Programs (B. Burt), 1988 (Box 60)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Epidemiology (D. Schottenfeld), 1988
        - Graduate Summer Session Program, 1988 (Box 60)
        - Victor M. Hawthorne New Investigator Research Award Grant, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Health Services Management and Policy (J. Griffith), 1988; 2 folders
        - Chairmanship Search Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 63)
      - Population Planning and Industrial Health, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Public Policy and Health Administration (G. Pickett), 1988 (Box 60)
    - National
      - Washington, D.C
        - General, 1988 (Box 60)
        - American Public Health Association (AIDS Working Group), 1988 (Box 60)
    - State
      - Ann Arbor, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Battle Creek
        - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Detroit, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Lansing
        - General, 1988 (Box 60)
        - Governor's Task Force on Access to Health Care, 1988 (Box 60)
        - Maternal and Infant Task Force on AIDS, 1988 (Box 60)
        - Public Health Advisory Council, 1988 (Box 60)
    - University
      - Campus Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Budget Priorities Committee, 1988; 3 folders (Box 60)
      - Center for Occupational Health and Safety Engineering, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Horace H. Rackham Graduate School (J. D'Arms), 1988 (Box 60)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1988 (Box 60)
        - Department of Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Michigan Journalism Fellows, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Michigan Sea Grant College Program, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) Merit Review, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs
        - General, 1988 (Box 60)
        - James Duderstadt, 1988 (Box 60)